<addon
  id="skin.aeon.nox"
  version="4.0.4"
  name="Aeon Nox"
  provider-name="Big_Noid &amp; phil65">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="4.0.0"/>
    <import addon="script.favourites" version="3.2.4"/>
    <import addon="script.playlists" version="0.1.1"/>
    <import addon="script.tv.show.next.aired" version="4.1.20"/>
    <import addon="script.artwork.downloader" version="12.0.2"/>
    <import addon="script.artistslideshow" version="1.3.2"/>
    <import addon="script.globalsearch" version="0.2.5"/>
	<import addon="script.playalbum" version="0.0.6"/>    
	<import addon="script.randomandlastitems" version="2.0.0"/>
    <import addon="service.skin.widgets" version="0.0.13"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.gui.skin"
    defaultthemename="Textures.xbt"
    debugging="false"
    effectslowdown="0.75">
    <res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="1080i" />
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="be">Aeon Nox 4.0 by Big_Noid &amp; phil65</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Aeon Nox 4.0 per Big_Noid &amp; phil65</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Aeon Nox 4.0 od Big_Noid &amp; phil65</summary>
    <summary lang="da">Aeon Nox 4.0 af Big_Noid &amp; phil65</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Aeon Nox 4.0 by Big_Noid &amp; phil65</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Aeon Nox 4.0 από τους Big_Noid &amp; phil65</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Aeon Nox 4.0 by Big_Noid &amp; phil65</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Aeon Nox 4.0 por Big_Noid &amp; phil65</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Aeon Nox 4.0 por Big_Noid &amp; phil65</summary>
    <summary lang="et">Aeon Nox 4.0 autoritelt Big_Noid ja phil65</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">Aeon Nox 4.0, tekijät Big_Noid &amp; phil65</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Aeon Nox 4.0 par Big_Noid &amp; phil65</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Aeon Nox 4.0, készítette: Big_Noid &amp; phil65</summary>
    <summary lang="is">Aeon Nox 4.0 eftir BigNoid &amp; phil65</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Aeon Nox 4.0 by Big_Noid &amp; phil65</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">Aeon Nox 4.0 by Big_Noid &amp; phil65</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">Aeon Nox 4.0 nuo Big_Noid &amp; phil65</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Aeon Nox 4.0 door Big_Noid &amp; phil65</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Aeon Nox 4.0 autorstwa Big_Noid &amp; phil65</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Aeon Nox 4.0 de Big_Noid &amp; phil65</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Aeon Nox 4.0 por Big_Noid &amp; phil65</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Aeon Nox 4.0 (autori: Big_Noid &amp; phil65)</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Aeon Nox 4.0. Авторы: Big_Noid и phil65</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Aeon Nox 4.0 av Big_Noid &amp; phil65</summary>
    <summary lang="th">Aeon Nox 4.0 โดย Big_Noid &amp; phil65</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">Big_Noid &amp; phil65开发的Aeon Nox 4.0皮肤</summary>
    <description lang="be">Aeon Nox stands for eye candy and customization. There are many different views and options to present your media in the way you want it. The Home window is fully customizable. You can add up to nine custom main menu items, each with five custom sub-menu items. You can change the look with different styles and themes, add or remove widgets and disable menu and sub-menu items you don't use. Be sure to checkout the changelog to find everything that was added or changed!</description>
    <description lang="cs">Aeon Nox je symbolem krásy a široké škály upravitelnosti. Umožňuje vám vyladit vzhled podle vašich představ. Úvodní obrazovku lze upravit ve všech aspektech. Můžete přidat až devět vlastních položek do hlavního menu, každá takto vytvořená položka může mít pět položek v pod-menu. Je možné si vybrat různé styly a témata, přidat nebo odebrat widgety a zakázat nepoužívané položky. Nezapomeňte si také přečíst seznam změn při aktualizaci, aby jste zjistily co je nového!</description>
    <description lang="da">Aston Nox står for eye candy og valgmuligheder. Der er mange forskellige visningstilstande og muligheder for at præsentere din mediesamling, som du ønsker det. Hjemmeskærmen er fuldt ud åben for tilpasning. Du kan tilføje op til ni valgfrie hovedmenu-elementer, hver med fem valgfrie undermenu-elementer. Du kan ændre udseendet med forskellige stilarter og temaer, tilføje eller fjerne widgets og deaktivere menu- og undermenu-elementer, som du ikke bruger. Husk at tjekke changelog'en for at se alt der er blevet tilføjet eller ændret!</description>
    <description lang="de">Aeon Nox steht für Hingucker und eigene Anpassung. Es gibt viele verschiedene Ansichten und Optionen um Deine Medien so zu präsentieren, wie Du es willst. Das Home-Fenster ist vollständig anpassbar. Man kann bis zu neun eigene Hauptmenüeinträge mit jeweils fünf Untermenüs hinzufügen. Du kannst das Aussehen mit verschiedenen Themes und Stilen verändern, Widgets hinzufügen oder löschen und Menüeinträge, die Du nicht benötigst, deaktivieren. Schau ins Changelog um immer auf dem neusten Stand über neue Funktionen zu sein!</description>
    <description lang="el">Το Aeon Nox αντιπροσωπεύει την ομορφιά και την εύκολη παραμετροποίηση. Υπάρχουν πολλοί τύποι προβολής και επιλογές προκειμένου να παρουσιάζονται τα πολυμέσα σας με τον τρόπο που επιθυμείτε. Η Αρχική Οθόνη είναι πλήρως προσαρμόσιμη. Μπορείτε να προσθέσετε μέχρι και εννιά προσωπικά αντικείμενα στο κεντρικό μενού, το καθένα με πέντε προσωπικά υπο-αντικείμενα. Μπορείτε να αλλάξετε την εμφάνιση με διαφορετικά στυλ και μοτίβα, να προσθέσετε ή να αφαιρέσετε widgets και να απενεργοποιήσετε τα μενού και τα υπομενού που δεν χρησιμοποιείτε. Ελέγχετε το αρχείο με τις αλλαγές (changelog) για νέες προσθήκες και μεταβολές!</description>
    <description lang="en">Aeon Nox stands for eye candy and customization. There are many different views and options to present your media in the way you want it. The Home window is fully customizable. You can add up to nine custom main menu items, each with five custom sub-menu items. You can change the look with different styles and themes, add or remove widgets and disable menu and sub-menu items you don't use. Be sure to checkout the changelog to find everything that was added or changed!</description>
    <description lang="es">Aeon Nox es sinónimo de espectáculo visual y personalización. Hay muchos puntos de vista diferentes y las opciones para presentar sus medios en la forma que desee. La ventana principal es completamente personalizable. Usted puede agregar hasta nueve elementos de menú principal, cada uno con cinco submenú personalizado. Puede cambiar el aspecto con diferentes estilos y temas, agregar o quitar widgets y deshabilitar elementos del menú y submenú que no se usen. Asegúrese de repasar el registro de cambios 'changelog' para encontrar todo lo que se ha añadido y cambiado!</description>
    <description lang="et">Aeon Nox tähendab silmailu ja kohandusvõimalusi. Saadaval on palju erinevaid vaateid ja valikuid, mis võimaldavad sul oma meediat esitleda nagu seda soovid. Avaleht on täielikult kohandatav. Võid lisada kuni üheksa kohandatud peamenüü elementi, igaüks kuni viie valitud alammenüü nimetusega. Võid muuta välimust erinevate stiilide ja teemadega, lisada või eemaldada vidinaid ja keelata menüü või alammenüü nimetusi, mida sa ei kasuta. Ära unusta viimaste uuenduste nägemiseks kontrollida muudatuste logi.</description>
    <description lang="fi">Aeon Nox edustaa silmänkarkkia ja muokattavuutta. Käytettävissä on useita näkymävaihtoehtoja ja asetuksia jotta voit käyttää mediaasi juuri siten kuin sinä haluat. Päävalikko on täysin muokattavissa. Voit lisätä yhdeksän nimikettä päävalikkoon, kullekin viisi alivalikkoa. Voit muuttaa ilmettä eri tyyleillä ja teemoilla, lisätä tai poistaa widgettejä ja ottaa pois käytöstä sellaisia valikkjo- ja alivalikkoja joita et käytä. Muista tarkistaa muutosloki nähdäksesi mitä kaikkea on lisätty tai muokattu!</description>
    <description lang="fr">Aeon Nox est synonyme de régal pour les yeux et de personnalisation. Il y a beaucoup de vues différentes et d'options pour présenter votre média de la façon que vous souhaitez. La fenêtre d'accueil est entièrement personnalisable. Vous pouvez ajouter jusqu'à neuf éléments personnalisables au menu principal, chacun avec cinq sous-menus personnalisables. Vous pouvez changer l'apparence avec différents styles et thèmes, ajouter ou supprimer des widgets et désactiver des éléments du menu et des sous-menus que vous n'utilisez pas. N'oubliez pas de lire le changelog afin de voir tout ce qui a été ajouté ou modifié!</description>
    <description lang="hu">Az Aeon Nox  szemet gyönyörködtető felszín és tökéletesen testreszabható. Sok különböző nézetet és opciós lehetőséget felhasználva mutatja be a médiafájlokat úgy, ahogy szeretnénk. A Főmenü teljesen testreszabható. Kilenc fő menüpont, melyek mindegyike öt egyéni al-menüpontot tartalmazhat. Meg lehet változtatni a nézeteket, a különböző stílusokat, hozzáadhatók vagy eltávolíthatók a widgetek, letilthatók a menük és almenü elemek, ha nem kellenek. A Változási listában mindig megtaláljuk hogy az előző verziók óta mi változott és mivel egészült ki a felszín!!</description>
    <description lang="is">Aeon Nox stendur fyrir augnakonfekt og sérsnið. Það eru margir valmöguleikar og hægt að sýna margmiðlunarefni á ýmsan hátt. Heimagluggan er hægt að sérsníða að fullu. Þú getur bætt við allt að níu sérsniðnum hlutum í aðalvalmynd, hver með fimm undirvalmyndum sem þú getiur sniðið að eign vild. Þú getur breytt útlitinu með mismunandi stíl og þemu, bætt við eða eytt græjum og aftengt valmyndir og undirvalmyndir sem þú ekki notar. Ekki gleyma að skoða listann yfir breytingarnar en þar getur þú séð allar breytingarnar!</description>
    <description lang="it">Aeon Nox Vuol dire delizia per gli occhi e personalizzazione. Ci sono differenti tipi di visualizzazione per mostrare i "media " nella maniera che tu vuoi. Il menù "HOME" è totalmente personalizzabile. È possibile aggiungere fino a nove voci personalizzate nel menu principale, ciascuna con cinque sottomenù. Puoi cambiare l'aspetto con vari stili e temi, aggiungere o rimuovere widget e disabilitare i menù e sottomenù che non utilizzi. Leggi la lista dei cambiamenti per sapere tutto ciò che è stato aggiunto o modificato.</description>
    <description lang="ko">Aeon Nox는 시각적 즐거움과 사용자 설정을 제공합니다. 여러분의 미디어를 여러분이 원하는 다양한 방식으로 표현해 주는 많은 보기 형식과 옵션이 있습니다. 홈 윈도우는 완전하게 사용자 설정이 가능합니다. 9개의 메인 메뉴 항목을 추가할 수 있고 각각 5개의 사용자 하위메뉴를 추가할 수 있습니다. 각기 다른 스타일과 테마로 모양을 바꿀 수 있고 위젯을 추가, 삭제할 수 있으며 사용하지 않는 메뉴과 하위메뉴를 끌 수 있습니다. 추가되거나 변경된 모든 기능은 변경로그를 확인하기 바랍니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt">Aeon Nox tai specialiųjų efektų išraiška ir pritaikymas. Yra daug skirtingų požiūrių ir galimybių keisti savo medijas taip, kaip norite pritaikant pagrindinius langus. Jūs galite pridėti iki devynių pasirinktinių pagrindinių meniu punktų, kiekvienam priskyrus iki penkių sub-meniu elementų. Jūs galite pakeisti išvaizdą su įvairiais stiliais ir ekrano temomis, pridėti arba pašalinti valdiklius, ijungti ir/arba išjungti meniu ir sub-meniu elementus, katrų jums nereikia naudoti. Būkite tikri parsiųstoje teminėje išvaizdoje rasite viską ko jums reikia kas atitiktu visas jūsų fantazijas!</description>
    <description lang="pl">Aeon Nox znaczy przyjemność dla oka i kastomizacja. Jest tu wiele różnych widoków i opcji aby zaprezentować twoje media tak jak chcesz. Ekran domowy jest w pełni konfigurowalny. Możesz dodać aż do dziewięciu własnych pozycji w menu głównym, a każdy z pięcioma konfigurowlanymi pozycjami podrzędnymi. Widok możesz zmieniać za pomocą różnych styli i tematów stylistycznych, dodawać lub usuwać gadżety oraz wyłączać pozycje i podpozycje menu których nie używasz. Koniecznie sprawdź listę ostatnich zmian aby znaleźć wszystko dodatki i zmiany!</description>
    <description lang="pt">Aeon Nox introduz impacto visual e personalização, com inúmeras vistas e opções diferentes para apresentar a sua média da maneira que quiser. A página inicial é totalmente configurável. Pode acrescentar até nove itens de menu personalizados, cada um deles com cinco itens de sub-menu. Pode alterar o aspecto, com diferentes estilos e temas, adicionar ou remover widgets e deactivar os itens de menu e sub-menu que não utilizar. Não se esqueça de ler o changelog para saber as novidades e tudo o que mudou.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Aeon Nox  tem grande visual e poder de personalização. Há diferentes modos de visualizações e opções para apresentar a sua mídia da maneira que você desejar. A janela inicial é totalmente personalizável. Você pode adicionar até nove itens personalizados no menu principal, cada um com cinco itens personalizados nos sub-menus. Você pode mudar o visual com diferentes estilos e temas, adicionar ou remover widgets e desativar menu e sub-menu itens que você não usa. Certifique-se de fazer o checkout da changelog para encontrar tudo o que foi acrescentado ou mudado!</description>
    <description lang="ru">Принципы Aeon Nox — красивое оформление и возможности настройки. Имеется множество различных представлений и настроек, чтобы представить ваши файлы так, как вы хотите. Главное меню полностью настраиваемое. Можно добавить до пяти настраиваемых пунктов главного меню, каждый с собственным подменю из пяти пунктов. Кроме того, можно изменять внешний вид, используя различные стили и темы, добавлять или удалять виджеты, а также отключать неиспользуемые пункты меню и подменю. Информацию о новых возможностях и изменениях можно найти в списке изменений.</description>
    <description lang="sv">Aeon Nox står för ögongodis och anpassning. Det finns många olika vyer och alternativ att presentera din media på det sätt du vill ha det. Hemfönstret är helt anpassningsbart. Du kan lägga till upp till nio anpassade menyalternativ med vardera fem egna undermenyalternativ. Du kan ändra utseendet med olika stilar och teman, lägga till eller ta bort widgetar och inaktivera meny och undermeny objekt som du inte använder. Var noga med att kolla ändringsloggen att finna allt som lagts till eller ändrats!</description>
    <description lang="th">Aeon Nox มีจุดยืนในเรื่องรูปลักษณ์และการปรับแต่ง. ซึ่งมีมุมมองและตัวเลือกที่หลากหลาย เพื่อแสดงสื่อของคุณ ได้ในแบบที่คุณต้องการ. หน้าต่างหลักที่ปรับแต่งได้อย่างเต็มที่. คุณสามารถเพิ่มเมนูที่กำหนดเอง ได้มากถึงเก้ารายการในเมนูหลัก, ที่แต่ละเมนูมีอีกห้าเมนูย่อย. คุณสามารถเปลี่ยนมุมมอง ด้วยลักษณะและชุดรูปแบบ ที่หลากหลาย, เพิ่มหรือเอาออกตัวแขวน และปิดการใช้เมนูหรือเมนูย่อยที่ไม่ใช้งาน. อย่าลืมตรวจสอบ changelog เพื่อหาสิ่งที่เพิ่มเข้ามาหรือได้เปลี่ยนแปลงไป!</description>
    <description lang="zh">Aeon Nox皮肤注重视觉效果和定制功能，它提供了展示媒体的很多种视图和选项，以及主界面的全面定制支持。你可以添加最多9个自定义主菜单项，每个项目还可以有5个自定义子菜单项。你可以改变不同风格和主题的外观​​，添加或删除部件和禁用你不使用的菜单和子菜单项目。记得查看更新记录了解功能增加和变动情况！</description>
    <disclaimer lang="be">Aeon Nox is a skin based on the design of Aeon by djh_. A great deal of textures used are from Aeon and it's mods. All credits to the makers of these skins and mods.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="cs">Aeon Nox je založený na designu vzhledu Aeon od djh_. Mnoho použitých textur je z původního vzhledu Aeon a jeho modifikací. Veškeré zásluhy patří autorům skinu a modifikací.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="da">Aeon Nox er et skin baseret på designet til Aeon af djh_. En stor del af teksturerne, der bruges, stammer fra Aeon og dets mods. Al kredit til skaberne af disse skins og mods.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="de">Aeon Nox ist ein Skin, basierend auf dem Design Aeon von djh_. Ein großer Teil der verwendeten Texturen sind von Aeon und seinen Mods. Vielen Dank an die Macher der Skins und Mods.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="el">Το Aeon Nox είναι ένα κέλυφος βασισμένο στο σχεδιασμό του Aeon από τον djh_. Πολλά από τα γραφικά του προέρχονται από το Aeon και τα διάφορα mods του. Αποδίδεται αναγνώριση στους δημιουργούς αυτών των κελύφων και mods.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en">Aeon Nox is a skin based on the design of Aeon by djh_. A great deal of textures used are from Aeon and it's mods. All credits to the makers of these skins and mods.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es">Aeon Nox es una piel basada en el diseño de Aeon por djh_. Una gran cantidad de texturas utilizadas son de Aeon y ese mods. Todos los créditos a los productores de estas pieles y mods.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es_MX">Aeon Nox es una skin basada en el diseño de Aeon por djh_. Una gran parte de las texturas usadas provienen de Aeon y sus modificaciones. Todo el crédito para los creadores de estas skins y sus modificaciones</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fi">Aeon Nox on toteutettu ulkoasun Aeon pohjalta, tekijä djh_. Suuri osa tekstuureista on otettu käyttöön Aeon:sta ja sen mod:eista. Kaikki kunnia näiden ulkoasujen ja mod:ien tekijöille.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fr">Aeon Nox est un skin basée sur le design d'Eon par djh_. Une grande partie des textures utilisées sont d'Aeon et de ses mods. Tout le mérite aux responsables de ces skins et mods.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="hu">Az Aeon Nox felszín, az Aeon felszínen alapul :  djh_ -tól. A textúrák nagy része az Aeon felszínből , vagy módosított változatokból való . Köszönet azoknak, akit ezeket készítették.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="is">Aeon Nox er útlit byggt á hönnun Aeon eftir djh. Mikið af áferð er notuð frá Aeon og breytingum á því. Allt kredit fer til þessara hönnuða.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="it">Aeon Nox è una skin basata sul design Aeon di djh_. Molte delle texture usate sono recuperate da Aeon e le sue mods. Tutti i ringraziamenti vanno ai creatori di queste skin e mod.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ko">Aeon Nox는 djh_가 디자인한 Aeon을 바탕으로 하였습니다. 사용된 텍스처들은 Aeon과 변형판들에서 가져왔습니다. All credits to the makers of these skins and mods.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="lt">Aeon Nox teminė išvaizda yra grindžiama Aeon djh_ dizaino. Daug tekstūrų ir modifikacijų nuo Aeon</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pl">Aeon Nox jest skórką opartą na projekcie Aeon autorstwa djh_. Wiele spośród użytych tekstur pochodzi z projektu Aeon i jego modów. Wszystkie słowa uznania należą się twórcom tych skórek i modów.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pt">Aeon Nox é um tema baseado no design Aeon de djh_. Uma grande parte das texturas usadas vêm de Aeon e dos seus mods. Os créditos devidos vão para os seus criadores.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Aeon Nox é uma skin baseado no design da Aeon por djh_. Uma grande quantidade de texturas utilizadas são da Aeon e seus mods. Todos os créditos para os criadores destas skins e mods.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ru">Aeon Nox — это обложка, основанная на дизайне Aeon, разработанном djh_. Большое количество текстур взято из обложки Aeon и ее модификаций. Авторство принадлежит создателям этих обложек и модификаций.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sv">Aeon Nox är ett skal baserat på Aeon-designen av djh_. En stor del texturer användes från Aeon och dess moddar. All förtjänst till skaparna av dessa skal och moddar.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="th">Aeon Nox เป็นสกินที่ใช้พื้นฐานการออกแบบจาก Aeon โดย djh_. ในทุกส่วนของพื้นผิวที่นำมาใช้ ล้วนมาจากAeonและmodของมัน. เครดิตทั้งหมดขอให้แก่ผู้สร้างสกินและmodนี้.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="zh">Aeon Nox是在djh_的Aeon皮肤设计思路上发展而来。许多纹理图片来源于Aeon及其修改版。感谢这些皮肤和修改版的开发者。</disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
