<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="skin.aeon.nox"
  version="2.0.0"
  name="Aeon Nox"
  provider-name="Big_Noid">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="3.00"/>
    <import addon="script.favourites" version="3.1.0"/>
    <import addon="script.randomitems" version="3.0.4"/>
    <import addon="script.playlists" version="0.1.0"/>
    <import addon="script.watchlist" version="0.1.2"/>
    <import addon="script.tv.show.next.aired" version="4.1.10"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.gui.skin"
    defaultthemename="textures.xbt"
    debugging="false"
    effectslowdown="0.75">
    <res width="1280" height="720" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="720p" />
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Aeon Nox by Big_Noid</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Aeon Nox door Big_Noid</summary>
  	<summary lang="es">Aeon Nox por Big_Noid</summary>
	<description lang="fr">Aeon Nox utilise presque toutes les vues du skin d'origine Aeon, ces mods et les textures du thème Black. Confluence de Jezz_X est la base de ce skin. Tout le mérite aux responsables de ces skins et mods</description>
    <description lang="en">Aeon Nox started out as a mod of Aeon based on the Confluence skin. Since then it has evolved into a skin with much more views and support for all new add-ons.[CR]Most of Aeon Nox' views are based on the Aeon65 mod by phil65, while other views are original designs or based on views from other skins.[CR]Skins that were a great inspiration for the design of Aeon Nox include:[CR]- Aeon65 by phil65[CR]- Alaska Revisited by Hitcher (Episode view)[CR]- Fusion by Arcanthur (BigFan view)[CR]- reFocus by Jeroen (InfoWall view)[CR]- Xperience by Team Blackbolt (Posters view)[CR]- Simplicity by Team S3 (TV Guide)[CR]- Confluence by Jezz_X (code base)</description>
    <description lang="es">Aeon Nox comenzó como un mod basado en la piel Confluencia. Desde entonces se ha convertido en una piel con muchos más puntos de vistas y con soporte a todos los nuevos add-ons.[CR]La mayor cantidad de vistas de Aeon Nox se basan en el mod Aeon65 de phil65, mientras que otras vistas se basan en diseños originales o vistas de otras pieles.[CR]Pieles, que eran una gran fuente de inspiración para el diseño de Aeon Nox incluyen:[CR]- Aeon65 por phil65[CR]- Alaska Revisited por Hitcher (vista Episodio)[CR]- Fusión por Arcanthur (vista BigFan)[CR]- reFocus por Jeroen (vista InfoWall)[CR]- Xperience por Team Blackbolt (vista Posters)[CR]- Simplicity por Team S3 (Guía TV)[CR]- Confluencia por Jezz_X (código base)</description>
	<disclaimer>For bugs, requests or general questions visit the Aeon Nox subsection on the XBMC forum. [CR]This skin was designed for use with a remote! Mouse usage is not supported!</disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
